market-talk.net 2009-05-27

# Market-talk.net market logic not fantasy

Wed, January 16, 2008

### Privacy Policy

**Market-talk.net**   recognizes that personal privacy is an important issue, so we design, maintain and operate our services with the protection of individual privacy as one of our utmost concerns. Our readership and subscriber databases are securely maintained for the proprietary publication and distribution of selected newsletters, financial and economic data and timely news reports and notices. 

Information Obtained. When you register to receive any of our publications, we usually obtain, at the minimum, your name, your e-mail address and zip code. When you elect to “contact us,” we may obtain additional information including your name, e-mail address, phone number, address and company name. We utilize this information to respond to individual inquiries as appropriate and to send you selected newsletters, financial data and timely news reports and notices. From time to time, we may forward additional information to you including special offers from Market-talk.net or specially selected partners who offer products, services, or information which we believe may be of interest to our readership. 

Market-talk.net also collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser customarily makes available whenever you visit any website on the Internet or open an e-mail.  This information may include your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your access and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information on an aggregate basis, to analyze the readership trends of our e-mails and access to our publishing services.

Some of our newsletters, reports and notices as well as our website may include ads from third parties. In order to measure advertising effectiveness, we may employ cookies or action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons). Any information that is collected via cookies and action tags is maintained under the same security measures as employed for personal information. 

**As of April 8 2009, Google will also employ DART cookies.**

• Google as a third party vendor uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  
• Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.   
• Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Third Party Information Gathering**. From time to time, ads or messages we send to you or that we post to our website may contain links that take you away from the Market-talk.net message or web site, to third party landing pages or web sites that we do not control. We are not liable for any information you may choose to share with any third parties on their landing pages or web sites; we are not liable for and do not control how they might share the information that they collect from you.

**Information Sharing**. We do not sell Market-talk.net’s subscribers’ e-mail addresses to any third parties for any reason whatsoever. 

Non-personal information may be compiled for statistical purposes and provided to third parties. However, none of this non-personal data will include individually identifiable information.   
Information Security.  Market-talk.net diligently works to insure the integrity and security of our network and systems. Market-talk.net, however, cannot guarantee that our security measures will totally prevent third-party “hackers” from illegally obtaining access to such information.

Updating Your Information.  If you wish to update or change your information, you may go to our website and select “control panel.” The screen that appears allows you to update or change your e-mail address.

**Changes to This Policy**. This Privacy Policy may be updated at any time, at Market-talk.net’s sole discretion. We expect that most changes will be minor. However, from time to time the changes can be significant. In either case, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice on our website home page. The date of the last revision to our Privacy Policy appears at the end of this notice.

If you have any questions regarding our website or this Privacy Policy, please e-mail [info@market-talk.net](mailto:info@market-talk.net).
